<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>Helping All Little Things Blog</title>
        <link>https://helpingalllittlethings.org/blog</link>
        <description>Helping All Little Things Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fundraiser for Boba]]></title>
            <link>https://helpingalllittlethings.org/blog/boba</link>
            <guid>https://helpingalllittlethings.org/blog/boba</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Meet Boba, a remarkable 7-year-old guinea pig with a heart full of resilience and the spirit of a fighter. Boba has faced more than his fair share of challenges in his life, but he never gave up—and now, he needs our help to overcome his toughest battle yet. Boba has been diagnosed with lymphoma, and he’s scheduled to undergo surgery to remove a cancerous tumor. We are raising funds to cover the cost of his surgery and post-operative care, and every donation—no matter how small—will make a huge difference.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Meet Boba, a remarkable 7-year-old guinea pig with a heart full of resilience and the spirit of a fighter. Boba has faced more than his fair share of challenges in his life, but he never gave up—and now, he needs our help to overcome his toughest battle yet. Boba has been diagnosed with lymphoma, and he’s scheduled to undergo surgery to remove a cancerous tumor. We are raising funds to cover the cost of his surgery and post-operative care, and every donation—no matter how small—will make a huge difference.</p>
<p><a href="https://helpingalllittlethings.org/docs/Guinea%20Pigs/lymphoma">You can read more about lymphoma in guinea pigs here.</a></p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" alt="Boba" src="https://helpingalllittlethings.org/assets/images/boba2-83b79ced67f818221cc6c53d9385d81a.jpeg" width="1188" height="2048" class="img_ev3q"></p>
<h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="bobas-journey-a-true-survivor">Boba’s Journey: A True Survivor<a href="https://helpingalllittlethings.org/blog/boba#bobas-journey-a-true-survivor" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Boba’s Journey: A True Survivor" title="Direct link to Boba’s Journey: A True Survivor">​</a></h2>
<p>Boba’s story is one of courage and survival. He’s not just any guinea pig—he’s a warrior who has been through many health challenges over the years. At 7 years old, Boba has already lived a full life, but it hasn’t been without its struggles:</p>
<p>- <strong>Missing an Eyeball</strong>: Boba lost one of his eyes earlier in life, but that never slowed him down. He learned to navigate the world with one eye, always full of curiosity and determination.</p>
<p>- <strong>Surviving Bumblefoot</strong>: Boba also battled and beat bumblefoot, a painful condition affecting the feet of guinea pigs. With proper treatment, care, and a lot of love, Boba healed and bounced back stronger than ever.</p>
<p>Now, Boba is facing another hurdle: lymphoma. Despite his age and past health issues, Boba’s spirit remains strong, and we believe he deserves every chance to live out his golden years cancer-free.</p>
<h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="why-boba-needs-your-help">Why Boba Needs Your Help<a href="https://helpingalllittlethings.org/blog/boba#why-boba-needs-your-help" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Why Boba Needs Your Help" title="Direct link to Why Boba Needs Your Help">​</a></h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" alt="Boba&amp;#39;s tumor" src="https://helpingalllittlethings.org/assets/images/boba-275978e9456a89d2838a31efe5739ca5.jpeg" width="922" height="2048" class="img_ev3q"></p>
<p>Boba’s upcoming surgery is essential to removing the cancerous tumor, but it comes with significant costs, including:</p>
<p>- <strong>Surgical Expenses</strong>: The procedure to remove Boba’s tumor is complex and requires expert veterinary care.</p>
<p>- <strong>Post-Operative Care</strong>: After surgery, Boba will need specialized care to ensure a smooth recovery. This includes medications, follow-up vet visits, and supportive care at home.</p>
<p>As a small, volunteer-run animal rescue, we rely on the generosity of our supporters to give guinea pigs like Boba the medical care they need. Every dollar raised will go directly towards covering Boba’s surgery and recovery expenses.</p>
<h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="how-you-can-help-boba">How You Can Help Boba<a href="https://helpingalllittlethings.org/blog/boba#how-you-can-help-boba" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to How You Can Help Boba" title="Direct link to How You Can Help Boba">​</a></h2>
<p>We are asking for your help to give Boba a fighting chance. Here’s how you can support his surgery and recovery:</p>
<p>1. <strong>Donate</strong>: Every donation, no matter the amount, brings us one step closer to funding Boba’s surgery. Whether it’s $5 or $50, your contribution will make a difference.</p>
<p>2. <strong>Share</strong>: If you’re unable to donate, you can still help by sharing Boba’s story with your friends, family, and social media followers. The more people who know about Boba’s journey, the closer we’ll get to reaching our goal.</p>
<p>3. <strong>Send Love</strong>: Boba may not understand words, but he knows love and kindness. Leave a comment or message of support for Boba to let him know how many people are rooting for him!</p>
<h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="bobas-future-depends-on-you">Boba’s Future Depends on You<a href="https://helpingalllittlethings.org/blog/boba#bobas-future-depends-on-you" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Boba’s Future Depends on You" title="Direct link to Boba’s Future Depends on You">​</a></h2>
<p>Boba has shown time and again that he’s a survivor, and we believe he can overcome lymphoma with the right medical care. But we can’t do it without your help. Let’s rally together to support this brave little guy and give him the chance to live out his remaining years in comfort and good health.</p>
<p>Thank you so much for your generosity and compassion. Boba may be missing an eye, but he’s never lost his sight for the love and support around him. Together, we can help Boba fight this cancer and continue to live his best life.</p>
<h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="donate-today-to-help-boba-win-his-battle-against-lymphoma">Donate today to help Boba win his battle against lymphoma!<a href="https://helpingalllittlethings.org/blog/boba#donate-today-to-help-boba-win-his-battle-against-lymphoma" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Donate today to help Boba win his battle against lymphoma!" title="Direct link to Donate today to help Boba win his battle against lymphoma!">​</a></h2>
<p>❤ <a href="https://www.paypal.com/ncp/payment/8SJFNZQVMQ452" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">PayPal</a><br>
<!-- -->❤ <a href="https://account.venmo.com/u/haltrescue" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Venmo</a><br>
<!-- -->❤ <a href="https://cash.app/$Haltrescue" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">CashApp</a><br>
<!-- -->❤ <a href="https://bit.ly/halt-piggies" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Amazon Wish List</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>fundraiser</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New T Shirt Fundraiser!]]></title>
            <link>https://helpingalllittlethings.org/blog/tshirt2024</link>
            <guid>https://helpingalllittlethings.org/blog/tshirt2024</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Introducing Our New Rescue T-Shirts!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Introducing Our New Rescue T-Shirts!</p>
<p>We are beyond excited to announce the launch of our new t-shirts featuring our adorable brand-new logo! 🎉 These shirts are not only cute and comfy but also a wonderful way to show your support for our small animal rescue as we relaunch. Every purchase goes directly toward helping us care for our rescue animals, provide medical attention, food, and all the love they need. 🐹🐰</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" alt="New Helping All Little Things Logo Tee" src="https://helpingalllittlethings.org/assets/images/tshirt2024-b45a852b8310edd3e847d4af907de6a6.jpeg" width="513" height="490" class="img_ev3q"></p>
<p>Our t-shirts come in a variety of colors, so you can choose your favorite and wear it proudly knowing that you’re making a real difference in the lives of the animals we save. Whether you’re a long-time supporter or new to our community, this is a fun way to help while spreading awareness for our cause. Plus, who wouldn’t want to rock our adorable new logo? 💖</p>
<p>Help us continue our mission of rescuing and caring for the tiniest, most vulnerable animals by grabbing a shirt today. Thank you for being part of this amazing community—we couldn’t do this without you! 🌟</p>
<p>Head over to the shop now and pick yours up before they’re gone! 🛍️👕</p>
<p><a href="https://www.customink.com/fundraising/haltrescuestartup" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://www.customink.com/fundraising/haltrescuestartup</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>fundraiser</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Big Announcement]]></title>
            <link>https://helpingalllittlethings.org/blog/announce</link>
            <guid>https://helpingalllittlethings.org/blog/announce</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[We have exciting news to share! Helping All Little Pipsqueaks is evolving and will be going back to our original name, Helping All Little Things — an independent rescue dedicated to small animals and sanctuary care. While we are branching out on our own, we want to reassure you that nothing has changed in our friendship with The Pipsqueakery. We’re still great friends and will continue to collaborate! We are so grateful that Alex and the rest of the Pipsqueakery helped us get through these past tumultuous 4 years. Without them, we never would have survived as a rescue.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We have exciting news to share! Helping All Little Pipsqueaks is evolving and will be going back to our original name, Helping All Little Things — an independent rescue dedicated to small animals and sanctuary care. While we are branching out on our own, we want to reassure you that nothing has changed in our friendship with The Pipsqueakery. We’re still great friends and will continue to collaborate! We are so grateful that Alex and the rest of the Pipsqueakery helped us get through these past tumultuous 4 years. Without them, we never would have survived as a rescue.</p>
<p>This transition allows us to focus more closely on what we’re most passionate about: providing specialized care to small animals and offering sanctuary care to those in need. Meanwhile, The Pipsqueakery will continue their outstanding work with wildlife and domestic rescue, a mission we fully support and admire.</p>
<p>We’re proud to announce that Helping All Little Things is officially established as a 501(c)(3) organization in New Hampshire and we will continue to do rescue work along the East Coast.</p>
<p>You can still find us on the same social media platforms, and we hope you’ll continue to follow us and support our work as we embark on this new chapter.</p>
<p>Thank you for being a part of our journey — we couldn’t do it without you, and we’re excited for all the great things to come!</p>
<h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="follow-us-on">Follow us on:<a href="https://helpingalllittlethings.org/blog/announce#follow-us-on" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Follow us on:" title="Direct link to Follow us on:">​</a></h3>
<p><a href="https://www.facebook.com/HALTRescue/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Facebook</a><br>
<a href="https://twitter.com/HALT__rescue" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Twitter</a><br>
<a href="https://www.instagram.com/helpingalllittlethings/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Instagram</a><br>
<a href="https://mstdn.social/@haltrescue" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Mastodon</a></p>
<h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="support-us-with">Support us with:<a href="https://helpingalllittlethings.org/blog/announce#support-us-with" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Support us with:" title="Direct link to Support us with:">​</a></h3>
<p><a href="https://www.paypal.com/ncp/payment/8SJFNZQVMQ452" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">PayPal</a><br>
<a href="https://account.venmo.com/u/haltrescue" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Venmo</a><br>
<a href="https://cash.app/$Haltrescue" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">CashApp</a><br>
<a href="https://bit.ly/halt-piggies" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Amazon Wish List</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>