<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>Helping All Little Things Blog</title>
        <link>https://your-docusaurus-site.example.com/blog</link>
        <description>Helping All Little Things Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Big Announcement]]></title>
            <link>https://your-docusaurus-site.example.com/blog/announce</link>
            <guid>https://your-docusaurus-site.example.com/blog/announce</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[We have exciting news to share! Helping All Little Pipsqueaks is evolving and will now be known as Helping All Little Things — an independent rescue dedicated to small animals and sanctuary care. While we are branching out on our own, we want to reassure you that nothing has changed in our friendship with The Pipsqueakery. We’re still great friends and will continue to collaborate!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We have exciting news to share! Helping All Little Pipsqueaks is evolving and will now be known as Helping All Little Things — an independent rescue dedicated to small animals and sanctuary care. While we are branching out on our own, we want to reassure you that nothing has changed in our friendship with The Pipsqueakery. We’re still great friends and will continue to collaborate!</p>
<p>This transition allows us to focus more closely on what we’re most passionate about: providing specialized care to small animals and offering sanctuary care to those in need. Meanwhile, The Pipsqueakery will continue their outstanding work with wildlife, a mission we fully support and admire.</p>
<p>We’re proud to announce that Helping All Little Things is officially established as a 501(c)(3) organization in New Hampshire! You can still find us on the same social media platforms, and we hope you’ll continue to follow us and support our work as we embark on this new chapter.</p>
<p>Thank you for being a part of our journey—we couldn’t do it without you, and we’re excited for all the great things to come!</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>